<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Carson Black -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.Ikona</id>
  <icon type="remote" width="48" height="48">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/raw/master/data/org.kde.Ikona.svg</icon>
  <name>Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxIkonaxx</name>
  <summary>Ikona is a design companion to help you design icons</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">L'Ikona és un company de disseny per ajudar-vos a dissenyar les icones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ikona es un complemento de diseño que le ayuda a crear iconos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Ikona adalah sebuah pendamping desain untuk membantu kamu mendesain ikon-ikon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Ikona è un compagno di disegno che ti aiuta a disegnare le icone</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Ikona is een ontwerphulp om te u te helpen pictogrammen te ontwerpen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Ikona jest towarzyszem projektu pomagającym w projektowaniu ikon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O Ikona é um assistente de desenho que o ajuda a desenhar ícones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ikona är en designkompanjon för att hjälpa dig designa ikoner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Ikona — допоміжна програма для створення піктограм</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxIkona is a design companion to help you design iconsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Ikona is a design companion to help you design icons. It is designed to integrate with the KDE Plasma desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Ikona és un company de disseny per ajudar-vos a dissenyar les icones. Està dissenyat per integrar-se amb l'escriptori Plasma del KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Ikona es un complemento de diseño que le ayuda a crear iconos. Ha sido diseñado para integrarse con el escritorio Plasma de KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ikona adalah sebuah pendamping desain untuk membantu kamu mendesain ikon-ikon. Ini dirancang untuk mengintegrasikan dengan desktop KDE Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ikona è un compagno di disegno che ti aiuta a disegnare le icone. È progettato per integrarsi con il desktop KDE Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ikona is een ontwerphulp om u te helpen pictogrammen te ontwerpen. Het is ontworpen om te integreren in het KDE Plasma bureaublad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ikona jest towarzyszem projektu pomagającym w projektowaniu ikon. Został stworzony tak, aby zintegrować się z pulpitem Plazmy KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Ikona é um assistente de desenho que o ajuda a desenhar ícones. Está desenhado para se integrar com o ambiente de trabalho Plasma do KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ikona är en designkompanjon för att hjälpa dig designa ikoner. Den är avsedd att integreras med KDE:s Plasma-skrivbord.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ikona — допоміжна програма для створення піктограм. Її інтегровано із стільничним середовищем Плазми KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIkona is a design companion to help you design icons. It is designed to integrate with the KDE Plasma desktop.xx</p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.5.2.2" date="2019-07-12" urgency="high">
      <description>
        <p>This is the initial version.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <translation type="qt">Ikona</translation>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The welcome screen of Ikona</caption>
      <image type="source">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/blob/master/data/home-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The colourful icon view of Ikona</caption>
      <image type="source">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/blob/master/data/colour-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The colourful icon view of Ikona in dark mode</caption>
      <image type="source">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/blob/master/data/colour-screenshot-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The monochromatic icon view of Ikona</caption>
      <image type="source">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/blob/master/data/monochrome-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The colour palette of Ikona</caption>
      <image type="source">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona/blob/master/data/colour-palette-screenshot.png</image>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>
        uhhadd@gmail.com
  </update_contact>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/kde/ikona</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
</component>
