<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Carson Black -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.Ikona</id>
  <icon type="remote" width="48" height="48">https://invent.kde.org/sdk/ikona/raw/master/data/org.kde.Ikona.svg</icon>
  <name>Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">أيقونة</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxIkonaxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Ikona</name>
  <summary>Ikona is a design companion to help you design icons</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">أيقونة هي مساعدك في تصميم الأيقونات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">L'Ikona és un company de disseny per a ajudar-vos a dissenyar les icones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'Ikona és un company de disseny per a ajudar-vos a dissenyar les icones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ikona ist ein Assistent für die Gestaltung von Symbolen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Ikona is a design companion to help you design icons</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ikona es un complemento de diseño que le ayuda a crear iconos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Ikona on abivahend, mis aitab ikoone kujundada</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ikona ikonoak diseinatzen laguntzeko diseinurako osagarri bat da</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Ikona on suunnitteluavustaja suunnitellessasi kuvakkeita</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Ikona est un outil de conception pour vous aider dans la conception d'icônes.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Ikona é un acompañante de deseño para axudarlle a deseñar iconas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Ikona es un companin de designo per adjutar te a designar icones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Ikona adalah sebuah pendamping desain untuk membantu kamu mendesain ikon-ikon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Ikona è un compagno di disegno che ti aiuta a disegnare le icone</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Ikona는 아이콘 디자인 도우미입니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Ikona is een ontwerphulp om te u te helpen pictogrammen te ontwerpen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Ikon er eit hjelpeprogram for design av ikon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Ikona jest towarzyszem projektu pomagającym w projektowaniu ikon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O Ikona é um assistente de desenho que o ajuda a desenhar ícones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Ikona é um assistente de design para criação de ícones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Ikona je dizajnový sprievodca, ktorý vám pomôže navrhovať ikony</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Ikona je spremljevalka oblikovanja, ki vam pomaga oblikovati ikone</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ikona är en designföljeslagare för att hjälpa dig designa ikoner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Ikona — допоміжна програма для створення піктограм</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxIkona is a design companion to help you design iconsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 是帮助您设计图标的一个配套应用。</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">Ikona 是個能幫助你設計圖示的設計小幫手</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Ikona is a companion application that help you when designing icons. Ikona lets you visualize your icons in an environment similar to a Plasma desktop, access the Breeze color palette and export your icons in multiple sizes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تطبيق أيقونة هو تطبيق مصاحب يساعدك عند تصميم الأيقونات. يتيح لك أيقونة تصور أيقوناتك في بيئة مشابهة لسطح مكتب بلازما ، والوصول إلى لوحة ألوان بريز وتصدير أيقوناتك بأحجام متعددة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Ikona és una aplicació d'acompanyament que ajuda a dissenyar icones. L'Ikona permet visualitzar les icones a un entorn similar a un escriptori Plasma, accedir a la paleta de color del Brisa i exportar les icones en diverses mides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'Ikona és una aplicació d'acompanyament que ajuda a dissenyar icones. L'Ikona permet visualitzar les icones a un entorn similar a un escriptori Plasma, accedir a la paleta de color del Brisa i exportar les icones en diverses mides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Ikona ist ein Assistent, die Sie beim Entwerfen von Symbolen unterstützt. Ikona ermöglicht Ihnen die Visualisierung Ihrer Symbole in einer Umgebung, die einer Plasma-Arbeitsfläche ähnelt. Sie können auf die Breeze-Farbpalette zugreifen und Ihre Symbole in verschiedenen Größen exportieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Ikona is a companion application that help you when designing icons. Ikona lets you visualise your icons in an environment similar to a Plasma desktop, access the Breeze colour palette and export your icons in multiple sizes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Ikona es una aplicación auxiliar que le ayuda a diseñar iconos. Ikona le permite ver los iconos en un entorno similar a un escritorio Plasma, acceder a la paleta de color Brisa y exportar los iconos en diferentes tamaños.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Ikona on abirakendus hõlbustamaks ikoonide kujundamist. Ikona võimaldab ikoone visualiseerida Plasma töölauale sarnanevas keskkonnas, kasutada Breeze'i värvipaletti ja eksportida ikoone mitmes suuruses.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ikona ikonoak diseinatzean laguntzen dizun aplikazio osagarri bat da. Ikonak zure ikonoak Plasma mahaiganaren antzeko ingurune batean irudikatzen, Breeze-n kolore paleta atzitzen eta zure ikonoak neurri aniztunetan esportatzen uzten dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ikona on kuvakesuunnittelun apusovellus. Ikonalla voi tarkastella kuvakkeita Plasma-työpöytää muistuttavassa ympäristössä, käyttää Breezen väripalettia ja viedä kuvakkeita eri kokoihin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ikona est un outil de conception pour vous aider dans la conception d'icônes. Il vous permet d'afficher vos icônes dans un environnement similaire au bureau KDE Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Ikona es un application companion que te adjuta quando tu designa icones. Ikona te permitte visualisar tu icones in un ambiente similar a un scriptorio de Plasma, accede al paletta de color Breeze (Brisa) e exporta tu icones in  dimensiones multiple.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ikona adalah aplikasi pendamping yang membantu kamu saat mendesain ikon. Ikona memungkinkan kamu memvisualisasikan ikonmu di environment yang mirip dengan desktop Plasma, mengakses palet warna Breeze dan mengekspor ikonmu dalam berbagai ukuran.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ikona è un'applicazione di utilità che ti aiuta nella progettazione di icone. Ti consente di visualizzare le tue icone in un ambiente simile ad un desktop Plasma, di accedere alla tavolozza dei colori Breeze e di esportare le tue icone in più dimensioni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Ikona는 아이콘 디자인 도우미 프로그램입니다. Plasma 데스크톱과 같은 환경에서의 아이콘을 볼 수 있으며, Breeze 색 팔레트에 접근하고 다양한 크기로 아이콘을 내보냅니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ikona is een companion toepassing die u helpt bij het ontwerpen van pictogrammen. Ikona laat u uw pictogrammen zien in een omgeving gelijk aan een Plasma bureaublad, geeft toegang tot het Breeze kleurenpalet en exporteert uw pictogrammen in meerdere grootten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Ikon er eit hjelpeprogram for design av ikon. Du kan bruka det til å visualisera ikona i eit miljø som liknar på Plasma-skrivebordet, bruka farge­paletten Breeze og eksportera ikona i fleire storleikar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ikona jest przydatnym narzędziem do tworzenia ikon. Ikona umożliwia zobrazowanie ikon w środowisku podobnym do pulpitu Plazmy, dostęp do palety barw Bryzy oraz eksportowanie ikon do wielu rozmiarów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Ikona é uma aplicação auxiliar que o ajuda no desenho dos ícones. O Ikona permite-lhe visualizar os seus ícones num ambiente semelhante a uma área de trabalho do Plasma, aceder à paleta de cores Brisa e exportar os seus ícones com vários tamanhos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Ikona é um aplicativo complementar que ajuda você na criação de ícones. O Ikona permite visualizar seus ícones em um ambiente semelhante a uma área de trabalho Plasma, acessar a paleta de cores Breeze e exportar seus ícones em vários tamanhos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Ikona je sprievodná aplikácia, ktorá vám pomôže pri navrhovaní ikon. Ikona umožňuje vizualizovať vaše ikony v prostredí podobnom pracovnej ploche Plasma, pristupovať k farebným paletám ako Vánok a exportovať ikony do viacerých veľkostí.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Ikona je spremljevalna aplikacija, ki vam pomaga pri oblikovanju ikon. Ikona vam omogoča vizualizacijo ikon v okolju, podobnem namizju Plasma, kjer nudi tudi dostop do barvne palete Sapica in izvoz svojih ikon v več velikostih.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ikona är ett följeslagarprogram som hjälper dig vid design av ikoner. Ikona låter dig visualisera dina ikoner i en miljö som liknar ett Plasma-skrivbord, komma åt färgpaletten Breeze och exportera ikoner med olika storlekar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ikona — допоміжна програма, яка полегшить вам створення піктограм. Ikona візуалізує ваші піктограми у середовищі, яке подібне до стільниці Плазми, надає вам доступ до палітри кольорів Breeze та уможливлює експортування створених піктограму у декількох розмірах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIkona is a companion application that help you when designing icons. Ikona lets you visualize your icons in an environment similar to a Plasma desktop, access the Breeze color palette and export your icons in multiple sizes.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 是一个帮助您设计图标的配套应用。 Ikona 可以让您在类似 Plasma 桌面的环境中可视化您的图标、访问微风色板并导出多个大小的图标。</p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.5.2.2" date="2019-07-12" urgency="high">
      <description>
        <p>This is the initial version.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <translation type="qt">Ikona</translation>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The welcome screen of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">شاشة الترحيب لأيقونة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La pantalla de benvinguda a l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">La pantalla de benvinguda a l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Úvodní obrazovka Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Der Startbildschirm von Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">The welcome screen of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La pantalla de bienvenida de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Ikona tervitusekraan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikonaren ongietorri pantaila</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ikona tervetulonäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">L'écran de bienvenue d'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">A pantalla de benvida de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Le schermo de benvenite de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Layar selamatdatang pada Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La schermata di benvenuto di Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Ikona 환영 화면</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het welkomstscherm van Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Velkomstbiletet i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Ekran powitalny Ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O ecrã de boas-vindas do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">A tela de boas-vindas do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Uvítacia obrazovka Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Zaslon dobrodošlice v Ikoni</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Välkomstskärmen i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вікно вітання Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe welcome screen of Ikonaxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 的欢迎屏幕</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Ikona 的歡迎畫面</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ikona/home-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The colorful icon view of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الأيقونات الملونة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">L'acolorida vista d'icones de l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'acolorida vista d'icones de l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Barevný pohled Ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Die farbenfrohe Symbolansicht von Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">The colourful icon view of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La vista de iconos a todo color de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Ikona värviline ikoonivaade</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikonaren ikono ikuspegi koloretsua</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ikonan värikäs kuvakenäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">L'affichage des icônes colorées d'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">A vista de icona de moitas cores de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Le vista de icone picoresc de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan ikon warna-warni pada Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La vista a icone colorata di Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Ikona 다색 아이콘 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De kleurrijke pictogramweergave van Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Fargerik ikonvising i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Barwny widok ikon Ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A vista do ícone a cores do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">A visualização em cores do ícone do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Farebný pohľad na ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Barvita ikona Ikone</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Den färgade ikonvyn i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд кольорових піктограм в Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe colorful icon view of Ikonaxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 的彩色图标视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Ikona 的彩色圖示檢視</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ikona/colour-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The colorful icon view of Ikona in dark mode</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الأيقونات الملونة في نمط المعتم</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">L'acolorida vista d'icones de l'Ikona en mode fosc</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'acolorida vista d'icones de l'Ikona en mode fosc</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Die farbenfrohe Symbolansicht von Ikona im dunklen Modus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">The colourful icon view of Ikona in dark mode</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La vista de iconos a todo color de Ikona en modo oscuro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Ikona värviline ikoonivaade tumedas režiimis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikonaren ikono ikuspegi koloretsua modu ilunean</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ikonan värikäs kuvakenäkymä tummassa tilassa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">L'affichage des icônes colorées d'Ikona en mode sombre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">A vista de icona de moitas cores de Ikona no modo escuro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Le vista de icone pictoresc de Ikona  in modo obscure</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan ikon warna-warni pada Ikona dalam mode gelap</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La vista a icone colorata di Ikona in modalità scura</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">어두운 모드에서의 Ikona 다색 아이콘 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">De kleurrijke pictogramweergave van Ikona in donkere modus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Fargerik ikonvising i Ikona i mørk modus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Barwny widok ikon w trybie ciemnym Ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A vista do ícone a cores do Ikona no modo escuro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">A visualização em cores do ícone do Ikona no modo escuro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Farebný pohľad na ikony v tmavom režime</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Barvit pogled na Ikono v temnem načinu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Den färgade ikonvyn i Ikona med mörkt läge</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд кольорових піктограм в Ikona у темному режимі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe colorful icon view of Ikona in dark modexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 在深色模式下的彩色图标视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">暗色模式中 Ikona 的彩色圖示檢視</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ikona/colour-screenshot-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>The color palette of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لوحة ألوان أيقونة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La paleta de colors de l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">La paleta de colors de l'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Barevná paleta Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Die Farbpalette von Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">The colour palette of Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La paleta de colores de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Ikona värvipalett</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikonaren kolore paleta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ikonan väripaletti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La palette de couleurs d'Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">A paleta de cores de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Le paletta de color de Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Palet warna pada Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La tavolozza dei colori di Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Ikona 색 팔레트</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het kleurpalet van Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Fargepaletten i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Paleta barw Ikony</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A paleta de cores do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">A paleta de cores do Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Farebná paleta z Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Barvna paleta Ikone</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Färgpaletten i Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Кольорова палітра в Ikona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxThe color palette of Ikonaxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Ikona 的色板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">Ikona 的調色盤</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ikona/colour-palette-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>
        uhhadd@gmail.com
  </update_contact>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/sdk/ikona</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
</component>
